ACTWU's Murray Finley Records from the President's Office 5619/036
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU's Murray Finley Records from the President's Office
1970-1987
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America
Murray Finley
5619/036
61 cubic feet
61 linear feet
Correspondence, reports, publications.
This collection consists of correspondence, reports, and files from the office of Murray Finley when he was the President (1972-1976) of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America and President (1976-1987) of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union.
6826793
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
July 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, July 2011
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related collections: 5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America 5619/004: ACTWU's Jacob Sheinkman Records from the Sectretary-Treasurer's and President's Offices 5619/004 mf: ACTWU's Microfiche Collection of Jacob Sheinkman's Speeches 5619/010: ACWA's Jacob Potofsky Files 5619/018: ACTWU's Secretary-Treasurer's Office Files 5619/036 mf: ACTWU's Microfilm of Murray Finley's Correspondence from the President's Office And all other 5619 collections.
Textile industry--New York (State)--New York; Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Clothing trade--New York (State)--New York; Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Finley, Murray, 1922-1995; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6826793
- Full Employment Action Council, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Full Employment Legislation, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Full Employment Board of Directors, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Full Employment Action Council, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO Convention- Employment, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Full Employment Action Council, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Murray H Finley, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Murray H Finley, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Full Employment, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Target Sportswear, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Congressman Andrew Young, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- I. W Abel, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- National Marine Engineers` Beneficial Association, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO Internal Dispute, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO Legislation, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Jan. A Ahlers- Germany, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Baltimore Joint Board, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Canadian Labor Movement, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Canadian Labor Movement, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Central States Board, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Central States Board, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Chicago Joint Board Insurance, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Chicago Joint Board Insurance, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Chicago Joint Board Insurance- Social Benefits, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Chicago Joint Board Insurance, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Chicago Joint Board Insurance, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Meeting in Cornwall, PA, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Scope and Contents
  August 9-10
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Cotton Negotiations, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Cotton Garments, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Cotton Garments, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Congressman John Dent, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- 1972 Election Campaign (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 1973 Election Campaign (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 1974 Election Campaign (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Farah- Cancellations, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Farah Clergy Correspondence, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Farah Clergy Correspondence, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Farah-Caravan Meeting, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Farah- Congratulatory messages, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Go Correspondence to Affiliates- Farah, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Farah- Film, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Farah- Murray Finley, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Farah- Financial Reports, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Farah, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Farah, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Farah, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Farah Programs, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Farah Publications, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Farah Legal, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Farah Legal, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Farah Publicity, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Farah Publicity, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Farah Publicity, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Farah Victory, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Farah- Support, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Farah- Responses, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Farah- Shipping, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Farah- Sponsors, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Farah Support, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Farah Student Program, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- ACWU- Financial Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Farah- Financial Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Father`s day council, 1974-1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Finley- European Trip, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  September 30
- General Executive Board- Requests for Increases in Dues, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board- Requests for Increases in Dues, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  January 28
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  September 16
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  June 24
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  October 24-25
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  June 4-7
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  March 5-9
- National Health Insurance, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- National Health Insurance, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Health Insurance, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Health Maintenance Organization, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Health Maintenance Organization, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Health Maintenance Organization, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- NY State Committee for Health Security, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- NY State Committee for Health Security, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Representative Elizabeth Holtzman Breakfast, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  January 20
- Import Demonstration, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  November 11
- Clothing Imports, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Imports, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Imports, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Insurance Fund- Financial records, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Insurance Fund- Financial Records, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Insurance Fund- Financial Records, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Insurance Fund, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Insurance Fund Pensions and Retirement, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Insurance Fund Pensions and Retirement, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- International Textile, Garment, and Leather Workers Federation, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Industrial Union department AFL-CIO, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Industrial Union department AFL-CIO, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Senator Edward Kennedy Conference, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  April 4
- Lane Kirkland dinner, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  December 12
- Laundry Workers Joint Board, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Under-Secretary General Bradford Morse Luncheon, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  June 18
- Occupational Safety and health, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Phillip Randall Institute, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Potofsky Medical Center, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Pre-paid Legal Services, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Research Department Report, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Research Department Report, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- General Reports and Studies, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- General reports and Studies, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- General Reports and Studies, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Senator Heinz Ruhnau Luncheon, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  March 27
- Single Pants, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Southern Department, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- South Jersey Joint Board, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Southeastern Regional Joint Board, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Claude Addison, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Jack Adier, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Eleni Aidonides, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Delores Archer, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Leona Austic, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Anastasia Ball, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Luis Barreto, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Basic Items Employees Local 768, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Max Becker, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Charles Bialostock, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Betty Birchmeier, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Josephine Boncore, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Patricia Bradley, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Mrs. George Bunting, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Arthur Burzio, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Mrs. A Caldwell, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Frank Caprio, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Rocco Carbone, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Rose Carmolingo, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Alberico Caroselli, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Ozie Carter, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Edward Cascarano, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Alexander Cassoni, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Louis Chillot, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Jo-Ann Cicerano, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Matilda Cioffi, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Lynda Corzine, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Gennell Cox, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Filippo Cozzupoli, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Anna L Cross, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Kenneth Crow, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Ferdinanda Czerwonka, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Darlene Dalton, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Hattie Daniel, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Sidney Davis, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Dominick D`Atri, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Olga De Angelis, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Florence De Beradinis, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Joyce Defino, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Margaret De Fino, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Angelo De Gregorio, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Philip De Martino, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Thelma De Pue, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Mario Di Cola, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Mary Eagles, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Mercedes Echazabal, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Excello Industry-Seymour, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Federal Employees, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Rebecca Myland, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Gladys Ellison, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Gennie Horn, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Beatrice Boerboom, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Mary Cromer, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Gladys Felda, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Rose Ferrugio, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Rosa Fernandes Filipe DePaolo, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Maria Forcillo, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Mary Formicola, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Janice Fortado, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Albert Forte Neckwear, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Edward Frank, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- Emma Funches, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Anna Galaggo, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Veronica Gamble, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Alberta Geisbrecht, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- Gennuso, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Arzelia Giles, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 72)
- Helen Giordano, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Jean Golden, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 74)
- Michael Gonz, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 75)
- Rose Marie Goshorn, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 76)
- Thomas Gottily, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 77)
- Philip Gratsch, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 78)
- Max Gray, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 79)
- Mary Grego, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 80)
- Herta Griskenas, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 81)
- Joseph Guggino, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 82)
- Halls, Tennessee, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 83)
- Margaret Hann, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 84)
- Agnes Heller, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 85)
- Annie Hildahl, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 86)
- Elva Hoitman, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 87)
- Marie Hoat, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 88)
- Edna Hunter, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 89)
- Ruth Jackson, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 90)
- J and B Sportswear, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 91)
- Agnes Jesmin, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 92)
- Regina Johnsey, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 93)
- Armetha Johnson, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 94)
- Ernestine Johnson, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 95)
- Kathleen Jones, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 96)
- Dorothy Jordan, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 97)
- Joseph and Feiss, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 98)
- Sylvia Kakoutis, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 99)
- Pauline Kauffman, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 100)
- Kathleen Kelley, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 101)
- Peggy Kerving, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 102)
- Sidney Koch, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 103)
- Ethel Konzal, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 104)
- Julia Kramer, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 105)
- Mildred Krause, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 106)
- Mildred Kramer, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 107)
- Opal Lamkin, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 108)
- Anthony La Placa, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 109)
- Anthony Lavalva, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 110)
- Nora Law, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 111)
- Dora Leichte, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 112)
- Beulah Lemon, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 113)
- Local 119B, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 114)
- Local 90 Palm Beach Pants Shop, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 115)
- Local 340 A, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 116)
- Local 402 Chase Bag, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 117)
- Local 640 Alabama, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 118)
- Local 643, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 119)
- Local 664, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 120)
- Local 920, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 121)
- Local 972, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 122)
- Local 1855, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 123)
- Catherine Mac Innis, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 124)
- John Maglieri, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 125)
- Angela Martino, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 126)
- Pearl Mary Martino, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 127)
- Lorraine T Masse, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 128)
- Rosa Matthews, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 129)
- Alfred Mattioli, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 130)
- Margie Mayer, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 131)
- Mary Mazzafera, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 132)
- Alice McClure, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Kathryn McCreless, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Evelyn Medeiros, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Maria Mederios, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Maria Mesuraca, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Nettie Metcalf, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Frances Meyer, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Catherine Miller, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Fannie Lew Miller, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Lillian Miller, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Lula Miller, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Margaret Miller, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Steve Morabito, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Edith Motha, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Catherine Murray, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Elda Myers, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Mary Naworth, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- George Nichola, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Mary Nocella, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Rose Nordiello, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Jane Otoski, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Erika Outland, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Clara Paci, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Roxie Lee Parks, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Frank Partipilo, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Blanche pautot, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Caterina Pedulla, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Iona Pierce, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Mrs. Pinkowski, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- James Peck, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Francis Pokigo, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Complaints from Members, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Sophie Potoreiko, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Ida Provenzano, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Carol Pugh, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Lydia Rathbun, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Blanche Reed, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Dorothy Reilly, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Veronika Romanovicz, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Anthony Rosalia, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Anna Rumery, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Stella Sanford, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Irma Scarpa, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Marie Schneberger, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Evelyn Settle, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Gretchen Simmons, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Francesco Sinisgalli, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Jeannette Slavin, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Alta Slusser, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Fannie Pearl Smith, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Gaetana Smith, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Evert Straks, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Katherine Sterle, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Bertha Steinberg, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Sterritt, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Edna Stiles, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Elizabeth Szendi, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Hazel Taber, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Francis Travis, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Catherine Thaxter, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Francis Travis, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Frannie Trozzo, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Toxeco, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Stella Tudor, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Ann Tulone, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Frances Vojkofsky, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Helen Von Almen, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Cleonie Watson, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Jeanette Weaver, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Philip Weiner, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Weld Incorporated, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Mary Alice Winkle, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Xerographical Davison, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Dan Zammiello, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Paul Zimmerman, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 74)
- Complaints, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 75)
- Complaints, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Complaints, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 77)
- Complaints, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 78)
- Complaints, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 79)
- Complaints, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 80)
- Executive Council Meeting, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  February
- AFL-CIO General Correspondence, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- AFL - CIO General Correspondence, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- AFL - CIO General Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- AFL - CIO General Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Services and Allied Forces Joint Board, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)